Nut up or shut up.
Zombieland is a comedy, horror film directed by Ruben Fleischer.
Columbus has made a habit of running from what scares him.
Tallahassee doesn't have fears.
If he did, he'd kick their ever-living ass.
In a world overrun by zombies, these two are perfectly evolved survivors.
But now, they're about to stare down the most
terrifying prospect of all: each other.
Columbus, played by Jesse Eisenberg.
Tallahassee, played by Woody Harrelson.
Wichita, played by Emma Stone.
Little Rock, played by Abigail Breslin.
406, played by Amber Heard.
Bill Murray, played by Bill Murray.
Zombieland is a 2009 American post-apocalyptic zombie comedy film directed by Ruben
Fleischer, in his directorial debut, and written by Rhett Reese and Paul Wernick.
It stars Woody Harrelson, Jesse Eisenberg, Emma
Stone, Abigail Breslin and Bill Murray.
In the film, four survivors of a zombie apocalypse, Tallahassee (Harrelson), Columbus (Eisenberg), Wichita (Stone) and Little Rock (Breslin)
make their way on an extended cross-country road trip to find a sanctuary free from an evil virus that turns people into zombies.
Development for Zombieland began in 2005, when Reese and Wernick
originally wrote the film as a spec script for a television pilot.
Fleischer helped develop the teleplay into a
screenplay for a self-contained feature.
Tony Gardner was hired as the film's special effects makeup designer, which
primarily features physical prosthetics to create the look of the zombies.
Principal photography for the film began in February 2009 and lasted until that March, with
filming locations including Hollywood, Atlanta and in and around Georgia.
Some of the film's scenes contained improvisation by the actors.
Zombieland premiered at Fantastic Fest on September 25, 2009, and was theatrically
released in the United States on October 2, by Sony Pictures Releasing.
The film received positive critical reception, with praise for its
screenplay, dialogue, comedy, and cast performances.
It grossed $102 million worldwide, becoming the
tenth-highest grossing zombie film in the U.S.
until the release of World War Z (2013), and $54 million in home sales.
A sequel, Zombieland: Double Tap, was released in October 2019.
The film explores themes of washington dc, usa, sibling
relationship, circus, post-apocalyptic future, gore.
The tone is lighthearted and dark.